-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕由cece&飞飞倾情奉献，仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
--------------------------
飞飞 LOVE 西西宝贝
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
制作:飞飞
校对:西西
组长：cece
-==cece&飞飞==-
老爸老妈的罗漫史
第一季 第九集
how i met your mother
Season 1 Episode 9
孩子们, 这是个
关于感恩节的故事
Kids,this is a thanksgiving story.
纽约的感恩节很棒
Thanksgiving in New York is a wonderful time.
是让自己想想身边的
It's a time for giving of yourself,
朋友的时候
for thinking of your fellow man.
也是让一坐冷漠的城市
A time when the unforgiving city
变的有点人情味的时候
becomes a little kinder.
嗯, 我刚才吐了
Well,I just ralphed.
你们这些家伙昨晚喝了多少?
How much did you guys drink last night?
不是多少... 是喝了什么?
Not how much... what?
感恩马天尼
The thankstini.
一种我发明的新奇的
A fun and delicious
有趣又可口的酒
new novelty drink I invented.
越橘汁
Cranberry juice,
土豆伏特加, 和一块浓缩汤料
potato vodka,and a bouillon cube.
喝起来就象火鸡宴
Tastes just like a turkey dinner.
嗯, 好象把感恩节喝在我嘴里!
Mmm,it's like thanksgiving in my mouth!
想要好喝的节日酒吗
You want a good holiday drink,
试试他的kwanzaapolitan
try his kwanzaapolitan.
公车来啦!
the shuttle's here!
从圣诞节到现在
He hasn't been back home
他就没有回过明尼苏达州了
to Minnesota since christmas.
他有点太激动了
He's a little excited. Lily,
得让车等等我们
we're holding up the shuttle.
你东西都带好了吗
牙刷
--Do you have everything you need
--toothbrush,
睡衣, 内裤? 内裤!
pajamas,underpants? Underpants!
那么, Lily... Marshall家
So,lil... Marshall's family.
整周和未来的家人在一起, 激动吧
Whole weekend with the future in-laws.
You excited?
是啊, 不会, 会很开心的我们
Yeah,no,it'll be fun.
Lily, 你只要说, "是啊, 不会"
Lily,you just said,"yeah,no."
我有吗? 不
Did I?No.
我- 我喜欢Marshall的家人
I-I love Marshall's family .
但是是啊,不会, 会很不错
But yeah,no,it'll be great.
你又说了一遍
You just did it again.
是啊, 不会, 闭嘴
Yeah,no,shut up.
那你感恩节不回家吗?
So you're not going home for thanksgiving?
不回, 我周五得工作
你呢?
No,I have to work on friday.
You?
我是加拿大人, 记得吗?
I'm Canadian,remember?
我们在十二月庆祝感恩节
We celebrate thanksgiving in October.
噢, 是啊, 我忘了
你们是些奇怪的家伙
Oh,right,I forgot.You guys are weird.
你们把"out" 发音为"oat"
You pronounce the word "out," "oat."
你们这些家伙是世界手枪暴力的领袖
You guys are the world's leader in handgun violence,
你们的健康系统一团糟
your healthcare system is bankrupt,
你的国家几乎在每件
and your country is deeply divided on
大事上都有严重分歧
almost every important issue.
你们把警察叫作骑警
Your cops are called "mounties."
那你一会要和Barney出去混吗?
So probably hanging out with Barney,then?
不，Barney要按
他自己的传统过感恩节
No.Barney's got his own thanksgiving tradition.
拖衣舞俱乐部的感恩节
Thanksgiving in a strip club.
谁加入?
Who's in?
强壮的豹女有一场惊奇的感恩节搏斗
The lusty leopard has a surprisingly good thanksgiving buffet.
另外还有
Heather装扮成朝圣者
Plus they do this thing:
Heather dresses up as a pilgrim,
Misty装扮成印地安人
and Misty dresses up as an Indian,
然后它们分享一块肉
and they share a meal together.
噢, Barney
Oh,Barney.
抱歉... 美国土著人
I'm sorry... native American.
我觉得我应该去
流浪者之家, 帮忙准备食物
I think I'm going to a
homeless shelter,serve food.
这太棒了!
That's awesome!
是啊，我觉得我应该
在这天做些好事, 你说呢?
Yeah,I though I'd just spend
the day giving back,you know?
做些好事
Doing some good.
取消和Barney的约会
Canceling out Barney.
当然
Exactly.
我的内裤都去哪了!
Where are all my underpants!
你检查过你的行礼箱了吗?
Did you check your suitcase?
我们走!
Let's go!
他们走了...
and go they went...
一直到明尼苏达圣克劳德州
all the way to St.
Marshall的家乡
Cloud,minnesota,marshall's hometown.
当Lily走进
And as lily stepped into
她未婚夫的家时
her fiance's boyhood home,
受到了热烈的欢迎
she received a big welcome.
嗨, 我们回来了! 嗨... 嘿...
Hello,we're home! Hello... hey...
非常盛大的欢迎
a very big welcome.
你们看, 六英尺四的
You see,at six-foot-four,
Marshall在Eriksen家族中
marshall was the runt
算矮的了
of the Eriksen clan.
哇, 我都忘了你们有这么高了
Wow,I forgot how tall you guys are.
我的未来媳妇呢?
Ere's my almost daughter-in-law?
我在这呢!
Here I am!
噢... 噢, 你给自己找了个
不错的小新娘, 儿子
Oh... oh,you got yourself
a great little bride here,son.
好了, 现在 别浪费时间了!
All right,now. No fartin' around!
把你们的冰鞋衬垫穿上
小伙子们!
Put your skates and your pads on,boys!
五分钟内开始游戏!
Game on in five minutes!
耶, 好
噢, 你们要玩冰球吗?
Yeah,all right. Oh,you're gonna play hockey?
用篮球?
With a basketball?
嗯, 这是那两种运动的结合
Well,it's sort of a combination of the two.
我们叫它篮冰球
We call it basice-ball.
我们发明的
We invented it.
这是世界上最危险
和最好玩的运动
It's the most dangerous
and awesome sport in the world.
篮冰球?
Bask-ice-ball?
不是冰篮球吗?
Not ice-ketball?
冰篮球?
Ice-ketball?
这名字听起来好怪
That just sounds weird.
是篮冰球, 好吗?
It's bask-ice-ball,okay?
我是玩的最棒的
And I'm the best.
你做梦
You wish.
嗯, 可能那只是
你还没见过我玩
Well,maybe that's
just 'cause you haven't seen me play.
噢... 我不知道, 亲爱的
Oh... I don't know,honey.
这不是适合女孩的运动
It's not really a sport for a girl.
嗯, 这样说很好笑
你的弟弟就丢的象个女孩
Well,that's funny,
because your brother throws like a girl.
噢... Marcus!
Oh... marcus!
这会很棒的
This is going to be great.
我知道
I know.
我们要做这个我好激动
I'm so psyched we did this.
看看这些人
Look at all these people,
放弃感恩节来帮助人
giving up their thanksgiving to help their fellow man.
这些是纽约最好的人了
These have got to be the best people in New York.
...给外婆家的...
打扰下, 伙计们
...To grandmother's house... excuse me,guys.
过去下
Coming through.
Barney?
嗯, 嗨伙计们
Well,hi guys.
你在这干嘛?
What are you doing here?
噢, 只是些上帝的工作
Oh,just the lord's work.
但你是撒旦
But you're Satan.
伙计们, 好吧, 听着
Guys,okay,look.
我不是受聘于这
我在这当义工
I don't advertise it,but I volunteer here.
我觉得帮助穷人是很重要的
I think it's important to help the less fortunate.
我是帅男版的Angelina Jolie
（安吉利娜朱丽是联合国亲善大使）
I'm the Angelina Jolie of incredibly hot guys.
这是在开玩笑吧, 是不?
This is a joke,right?
你不是真是在当志愿者吧
You don't actually volunteer here.
Barney, 我们需要你过去
Barney,we need you out front.
分配食物那里太挤了
There's a logjam on the stuffing line.
你能告诉他们该怎么做吗?
Can you show them how it's done?
我就去
I'm on it.
等等, 难道这是真的吗?
Wait,so this is real?
Barney在干这个?
Barney does this?
每周日, 整年都要
Every Sunday,all year long.
他是我们最棒的志愿者
He's our best volunteer.
因为我是被最棒的人
训练出来的, Kendall
That's 'cause I was trained by the best,Kendall.
不管怎样, 我们
自愿来这, Kendall
Anyway,we're psyched to be here,Kendall.
有什么需要我们做的?
What do you need us to do?
呃, 回家 我们人手够了
Uh,go home. We're full.
什么?
What?
我们是志愿者
我们是免费劳力
We're volunteers.We're unpaid help.
免费的劳力怎么会嫌少呢?
Can you ever really have enough unpaid help?
一年里志愿者最多的一天?
On the biggest volunteer day of the year?
对, 可以
Yeah,you can.
拜托, 我们只是想帮帮忙
Come on,we just want to help out.
Kendall, 他们不错
Kendall,they're cool.
好吧, 但是我不保证任何事
Fine,but I'm not promising anything.
在这等着
需要你们的时候会让你们知道
Wait here
We'll let you know if we need you,
好吧, 嗯, 我得到外面去
Okay,well,I'd better get back out there.
有很多食物要分发
There's a lot of food to give out.
还有许多微笑
And a lot of smiles.
噢, 我差点忘了
Oh,I almost forgot.
我知道还太早了, 但...
你是未来的Eriksen夫人
I know it's early,but...
you are a future mrs.Eriksen.
谢谢!
Thank you!
嗯, 我穿起来很合适
Well,it'll go great with me,
呃... 我很喜欢
uh... I just love it.
好了, Lily, 我们要安排你做色拉
Okay,lily,we're putting you on salad duty.
噢, 我会用鲜虾甜辣汁
Oh,l make this great frisee and endive salad
做很棒的蔬菜色拉
with a coriander-lime vinaigrette.
但是今天是美国节日
But this is an American holiday.
Lily, 你就快成为Eriksen夫人了
Lily,now that you're going to be a mrs.Eriksen,
我会让你知道
我们的秘密食谱
I'm going to let you in on a secret recipe:
Eriksen家族七层色拉
The Eriksen family seven-layer salad.
七层色拉?
Seven-layer salad?
六杯蛋黄酱?
"Six cups of mayonnaise"?
不可能吧
That can't be right.
噢, 不是, 亲爱的 是十六杯
Oh,no,dear. 16 cups.
蛋黄酱在那边的橱柜里
Mayo's in that cabinet.
噢, 我的天
Oh,my god.
外面的篮冰球游戏正激烈进行
There is some serious bask-ice-ball going on out there.
爸用雪球打到了Marcus的脸
Dad totally nailed marcus in the face with a snowball,
这太傻了
which is a foul,
因为只能用一次雪球
'cause you only get one snowball per possession,
我用我的冰鞋打到他的胫节
so I nailed him in the shin with
然后就投进了!
my skate and I totally dunked it!
耶, 你一直坐着在看
Yeah,you were sitting pretty,
直到我用求棍打到你
till I whacked you with that mallet.
嘿, 好伙计
Hey,gorgeous.
你玩的开心不?
You having fun?
是啊, 但... 但我有点想你
Yeah,but... but I kind of miss you.
你能在这呆会吗?
Could you stay in here for a little bit?
好, 好, 好, 没问题
现在是中场休息
Yeah,yeah,yeah,no problem.
It's halftime.
噢, 休息结束!
把你们的屁股抬起来! 来吧
Oh,halftime's over!
Get your butts out here!Come on.
我希望你喜欢
冰鞋的味道, 呆子!
And I hope you like the taste of skate,dorko!
-去吧
-谢谢, 宝贝
Go.
Thanks,baby.
啊, 这很棒吧?
Aw,isn't this great?
你能知道为什么
Can't you see why
我的高中同学都呆在这了吧?
everyone from my high school stays in this town?
嘿, Marvin, 你是个呆子, 呆子
Hey,Marvin,you're the dorko,dorko.
天, 外面太让人激动了
Man,it's amazing out there.
我今天做了那么多好事
I've done so much good today,
我就象获得灵魂的升华
I've got like a soul boner.
天, 当你给穷人递上热的有营养的食物
Man,the way the faces of the less fortunate
他们脸上流露出的希望之光
light up when you give them a hot,nutritious meal.
还有什么能比这感觉更好吗?
Is there a better feeling on earth?
昨天你说世界上
最好的感觉是
Yesterday you said the best feeling on earth
was
吮吸脚趾
getting your toes sucked.
然后你和自己的脚掌击掌
Then you requested a high-five with your foot.
嘿, Barn, 让我们帮帮你吧
Hey,Barn,what do you say you let us sub in for you,
帮你舀食物?
scoop stuffing for a little bit?
你第一天来就想舀食物?
You want to scoop stuffing your first day out?
你好? 国家橄榄球联盟吗?
这周日我能当四分卫吗? 伙计
Hello?NFL?
Can I be quarterback this sunday? Dude.
好吧, 我已经把古米熊软糖放上了... 色拉
Okay,I finished the gummi bear layer of the... salad.
下一步是什么?
What's next?
薯片 当然
Potato chips.Of course.
那么, Lily...
So,lily...
你们什么时候考虑生小孩?
when are you gonna start thinking about having a baby?
小孩?
Baby?
呃, 你知道, 我还没认真想过这个问题，完全没有
Uh,you know,I hadn't really thought about it.At all.
事实上, Lily阿姨在撒谎
Actually,aunt lily was lying.
她现在脑子里想的都是这个
It was all she'd been thinking about.
你们看
You see,
记得她说... 嗯,我刚才吐了...
remember when she said... well,I just ralphed...
那时候
At that point,
她已经晚来了5天
she was five days late.
现在是第6天
This was day six.
对, 我说,生小孩
我还太年轻, 是不?
Yeah,I mean,I'm way
too young to have a baby,right?
噢, 你在开玩笑吗?
Oh,are you kidding?
我怀Marcus比你还小
I was younger than you when I had Marcus.
15磅的可爱小子
Beautiful 15-pound boy.
比这个火鸡大不了多少
Not much bigger than this turkey right here.
噢, 天
Oh,my.
现在, Lily开始对加入
now,if lily was already uneasy about joining
Eriksen一家犹豫了
the Eriksen family,
想象她对即将有一个15磅的Eriksen
imagine how she felt about possibly having
在她体内生长是什么感受
a 15-pound Eriksen growing inside of her.
真是个大婴儿, Judy
That's a big baby,Judy.
医生以为是双胞胎
The doctor thought he was twins.
双胞胎! 双胞胎!
Twins! Twins!
这太疯狂了!
This is crazy!
什么时候做善事变的这么难了?
When did it get so hard to do charity work?
我一直在做慈善工作
I do charity work all the time.
记得我说我要
帮你找女朋友吗?
Remember when I said I'd find you a girlfriend?
令人愉快
Delightful.
这个小工程要什么时候实施?
How's that little project coming along anyway?
我一直在努力
I'm working on it.
我将把你介绍给
你正在盯着看的那女孩
I'm gonna introduce you
to that girl you've been staring at.
什么? 这太疯狂了
What?That's crazy,
我没盯着任何女孩看...
I haven't been staring at any girl...
见过Ted吗?
have you met Ted?
嗨 我就是刚刚提到的Ted
Hi.I'm the aforementioned Ted.
这位是... 呃, 走掉了
And this is... um,gone.
我叫Amanda
I'm Amanda.
嗨
Hi.
那么, 呃……
你在这干什么, Ted?
So,uh,what do you do here,Ted?
嗯, 我... 呃, 什么也没
我什么也没干
Well,I' been... um,nothing.
I do nothing.
嗯, 如果你想做点什么
Well,if you want to do something,
你和你的女朋友能帮到
you and your girlfriend can help
把这些捐赠物分类
sort through these donations.
噢, 呃, 我不是他的女朋友
Oh,um,I'm not his girlfriend.
以前是, 但, 呃
I used to be,but,um,
我在感情和性事上都不适合Ted
I just wasn't enough woman for Ted emotionally or sexually.
噢, 我的天
Oh,my god.
那么, Amanda... 你需要我们做什么?
So,Amanda... what do you need us to do?
好吧, 这很重要
Okay,this is important.
查看这些捐赠食物
Go through all these boxes of food donations,
把好的食物放到这个盒子里
take out the really good stuff,
and put it into this box.
知道了
Got it.
分类
Consider it sorted.
嘿, 我们有事做了
Hey,we're in business.
嘿, 今天Barney不会独享所有的光环了
Hey,Barney's not gonna get all the glory today.
我们还是从这个开始吧
Let's start with this one.
好啊
Yeah.
阿门
Amen.
看看谁来说晚安啦
Look who came to say good night.
是小Martin 三个月大
It's little Martin. Three months old.
月?
Months?
三个月
Three months.
他在喝牛奶了
He's been drinking his milk.
她又怀孕了吗?
and she's already pregnant again?
嗯, 那是因为Eriksen家孩子
制造的“孩子”会游泳
Well,that's 'cause those
Eriksen boys can swim.
它们有两条尾巴头上有钻
They've got two tails and a drill bit for head.
爸, 你让我难堪了!
Dad,you're embarrassing me!
噢, 别担心, 儿子, 她不会介意的
Oh,don't worry about it,son,she's cool.
她就要变成Eriksen的一员了
She's going to be an Eriksen.
是啊 嗯,嗯, 法律上不是
Yeah.Well,well,not literally,
因为, 你知道我要保留我的姓氏
'cause,you know,I'm keeping my name.
但... 那围裙
But... the apron.
嗯, 我们还没决定
什么事情, 我们...
Well,we haven't actually
decided anything yet,so we're...
不是, 我决定要保留我的姓氏
No,I've decided and I'm keeping my own name.
但Eriksen是个好姓氏
But Eriksen is a great last name.
大家都知道Eriksen一家
People know the Eriksens.
嗯, 确实, 在圣克劳德州
Well,sure,in St. Cloud,
但是我们不会让孩子
在圣克劳德州长大 是不, 宝贝?
but our kids aren't going to be
growing up in St.Cloud.Right,baby?
嗯, 为什么不在圣克劳德州?
Well,why not St.Cloud?
我是说, 我喜欢在圣克劳德州长大
I mean,I loved growing up in St.Cloud.
圣克劳德州是个度过童年的好地方
St.Cloud is a great place to have a childhood.
嗯, 纽约也是
Well,so is New York.
什么? 就是
what?It is.
我们也成长的很好
And we grew up just fine.
我们长大合适大小然后就停止
And we grew to the proper size and then we stopped.
嘿, Amanda, 这盒东西是要来干嘛的?
Hey,Amanda,what's this box for?
噢, 是给我的
Oh,that's for me.
你可以放到我车上去
You can put it in my car.
你车上, 呃, 然后你就带回...家?
In your car,um,and then you'll take it...Home?
对啊, 我们有很多
多余的食物
Yeah,we get so much extra food,
没人能吃完
no one can eat it all.
噢, 松鹿油 太棒了!
Ooh,truffle oil.Score!
人们捐赠食物是因为
People donated this food
他们认为这会
拿去给挨饿的人
thinking it was going to feed the hungry.
我知道
I know.
我也很饿
And I'm starving.
但, Marshall, 你喜欢纽约
But,Marshall,you love New York.
是, 我喜欢, 但是你一直说我们有孩子后
Yes,l do,but you always said that when we have kids,
想搬出曼哈顿
you wanted to move out of Manhattan.
是啊, 去布鲁克林
Yeah,to Brooklyn.
为什么我们要讨论这个?
Why are we even talking about this?
这就象一路走到黑
This is like way down the road.
但Lily知道一路走到黑
But lily knew"way down the road"
也许并不那么远
might not be so far down the road.
我要去厕所
I need to go to the restroom.
Lily, 厕所在另一边
Lily,the restroom's the other way.
所以她走向那条路
So she literally headed down the road.
Lily? Lily!
lily?lily!
这么说你们今天没为
任何人做点什么
So, wait. Not only have you not done
any good for anyone today,
还帮别人从流浪者
you're actually helping someone
那里偷取食物?
steal from the homeless?
你知道, Ted, 今天是感恩节
You know,Ted,it's called thanksgiving,
不是感谢偷取东西的节,该死
not thankstaking,damn.
Barney, 你需要我给你
签报到簿, 是吧?
Barney,you needed me to sign your time sheet,right?
噢, 是啊, 对 谢谢
Oh,yeah,right.Thanks.
Barney
Barney.
嗯, 怎么了?
Yeah,what's up?
你要签报到簿吗?
You have a time sheet?
别人都没有报到簿
No one else has a time sheet.
对 那?
Yeah. So?
好吧, 让我看看
All right,let me see that.
拜托 这是我的隐私, 我的私事!
That's my private,personal business!
法庭服社会役令?
Court-mandated community service?
我的天, 你在缓刑期?
Oh my god,you're on probation?
你干了什么?
What did you do?
这是我的私人问题
That's my private,personal business.
我被不公证的惩罚了
I was unfairly punished
只是因为那面墙属于基督教堂
because the wall belonged to the judge's church.
你在教堂边撒尿?
You peed on a church?
是在小巷子里
I peed in an alley,
刚好有座教堂
which happened to have a church,
因为我喝醉了没有看到
which I did not see because I was drunk.
噢, 你是魔鬼
Oh,you are evil.
啊, 世界又正常了
Ah,all's right with the world again.
好吧, 好, 所以法官让我做这个
Okay,fine,so a judge is making me do this.
但我还是在做
But I'm still doing it.
而且做的很棒, 顺便说一句
And kicking ass at it,btw.
最后一次你们做好事是什么时候, 哈?
When's the last time either of you did something good,huh?
Kendall
Kendall.
啊, Kendall
Ah,Kendall.
Amanda从无家可归的
Amanda is stealing portabello
人们那里偷蘑菇
mushrooms from homeless people.
Amanda
Amanda.
我也想要那些蘑菇
I called dibs on the portabello mushrooms.
这些是给饥饿的人的
Those are for the hungry.
我知道 我很饿
I know. And I'm starving.
那些是很好的蘑菇
Those are good mushrooms.
蘑菇 蘑菇
Mushrooms.Mushrooms.
每个人都有蘑菇拿
Portabello mushrooms for everyone.
拿好它们然后跑掉!
Take them and run!
这些是很贵的
They're very expensive.
感恩节快乐
Happy thanksgiving.
感恩节快乐 哼
"Happy thanksgiving." Huh.
如果在这时候买验孕棒算快乐的话, 每个人都快乐
As in "check out the chick buying the knock-up test,everybody.
担心着会有什么结果?
Wonder what must be going through her head?
对, 嗯, 既然你问了
Yeah,well,since you asked,
一个喜欢蛋黄酱的巨人家庭
a family of mayonnaise-guzzling giants is trying to
要把我卷进乡村噩梦
suck me into their suburban nightmare,
而且很有可能我怀上了
and there's a solid chance that
15磅的Eriksen家型号的火鸡
I have an Eriksen the size of a 15-pound
正在我身体里滋长!
turkey growing inside of me!
噢, 你知道Eriksen一家?
Oh,you know the Eriksens?
你是Marshall的未婚妻
You're Marshall's fiancee.
太棒了
Fantastic.
很高兴见到你
So nice to meet you.
你比形容的要高
You are taller than described.
我很抱歉刚刚朝你大吼大叫
Look,I'm sorry I just yelled at you.
介意我用下你的卫生间吗?
You mind if I use your bathroom?
没有
Don't have one.
你要怎么办当你想...?
What do you do when you have to...?
憋着
I hold it.
你不能解雇一个志愿者
you can't fire a volunteer.
很显然可以
Apparently you can.
还有他的没有扔蘑菇的两个无辜朋友
And his two non- mushroom-throwing friends.
我不敢相信我会告诉
I can't believe I told
Kendall你们两个很不错
Kendall you guys were cool.
我只有40个小时
I have 40 hours left on
就可以完成我的服务役了
my community service
但现在我
and now I've gotta spend it
得在该死的林区拣垃圾
spearing trash on a freakin' median strip.
年度最佳志愿者!!
Volunteer of the year!!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉, 好吗?
I'm sorry,okay?
听着, 如果有什么我能弥补的
Look,if there's anything I can do to make it up to you
就告诉我
just tell me.
我会-我会做的
I'll-I'll do it.
Ted, 我很高兴你问了
Ted,I'm glad you asked.
Domo arrigato,mr. Roboto
domo... domo domo arrigato,mr.Roboto
出乎意料的好
surprisingly good.
是吧? 我就说
Right?I told you so.
公共场所小便
Public urination.
谁会因为在公共场所小便被捕?
Who gets arrested for public urination?
Lily被捕了
Lily's been arrested.
噢, 亲爱的 因为什么?
Oh,dear.What for?.
公共场所小便
Public urination.
谢谢你, Pete
Thanks,pete.
没问题, Marsh.
No problemo,Marsh.
你还好吧?
You all right?
不好
No.
我在你家人面前丢脸了
I embarrassed myself in front of your family,
然后现在又在最让人压抑的地方
and now I'm celebrating thanksgiving in
庆祝感恩节
probably the most depressing place ever.
Domarrigato,mr.Roboto
嗯, 我很高兴你很安全
well,I'm glad that you're safe.
嘿, 问个奇怪的问题
Hey,weird question.
为什么你要沿着23号线开3英里
Why did you drive three miles down route 23 and
去一家便利店后面小便?
take a pee behind a convenience store?
好吧, 我会告诉你
Okay,I'll tell you,
但在这之前
but before I do,
答应我我们不会搬来
promise me that we are not gonna move to
明尼苏达圣可劳德州
答应我！！
St.Cloud,Minnesota.
Promise.
我并没有说希望我们明天立马就搬来啊
I'm not suggesting that we move here tomorrow,
我只是...
答应就好了
I'm just...
promise.
为什么你希望我答应你这个?
Why do you want me to promise you that?
因为 我不适合这里
Because.I don't fit in here.
我没有8英尺高
I'm not eight feet tall,
我也不认为里面加了
and I don't think you could call it
油炸洋葱卷的沙拉算不上沙拉
a salad if it has funyuns in it.
我就是油炸洋葱卷
I'm funyuns.
还有蛋黄酱,还有古米熊软糖
And mayonnaise and gummi bears
和篮冰球
and bask-ice-ball,
我喜欢圣克劳德州
and I love St.Cloud.
还有, 是的
And,yes,
可能有一天我会想搬回来
there is a part of me that would like to move here someday,
但是为什么我们要在
and why are we having this discussion
感恩节的监狱里
讨论这个呢?
in a jail cell on thanksgiving?
好了, 你的私人物品,一个钱包
Okay,personal effects. One wallet.
一个手机 一个... 验孕棒
One cell phone. One... pregnancy test.
Pete在我看这个之前就逮捕了我
Pete arrested me before I could look at it.
哇
Whoa.
耶
Yeah.
Lily, 我们不能让我们的孩子玩篮冰球
Lily,we can't let our kids play bask-ice-ball.
篮冰球真的很危险
Bask-ice-ball is really dangerous.
是啊, 那游戏的规则到底是什么?
Yeah,what are the rules to that game,anyway?
没有规则
There are no rules.
我们互相乱叫
We just wail on each other.
听着, 我并不想和我的家族一个模子
Look,I don't want to be exactly like my family.
也不要误会我
And don't take this the wrong way,
但我也不想
but I don't want to be exactly
和你的家庭一个模子
like your family either.
我们应该有我们自己的家庭
We'll be our own family.
我们会找到
And we'll find our own way to
我们自己的方式抚养小孩
freak out the people our kids bring home
太好了, 我都哭了 听着
Great,now I'm crying. Look.
我们在十秒内可能会有
We may have some really big decisions
一个重大的决定需要我们去做
to make in about ten seconds.
但是现在, 我不在乎
But right now,I don't care
我们的孩子在哪长大
where our kids grow up.
只要你是父亲
As long as they have you for a father.
天, 我希望你是父亲
Gosh,I hope you're the father.
只是个缓和气氛的小玩笑
Just a little joke to lighten up the mood.
看看结果?
What does it say?
我害怕看
I'm afraid to look.
是阴性的!
It's negative!
噢, 感谢上帝
Thank god. Oh,thank god.
还有, 嘿!
And,hey!
Ted
Ted.
你在听吗?
Are you listening?
你是个不错的家伙
You're a good guy.
想知道为什么我明天得工作吗?
Want to know why I have to work tomorrow?
我们公司在为烟草公司
My firm's designing
办行政休息室
an executive lounge for tobacco company.
和癌症对抗
In the fight against cancer,
我是癌症那边的
I'm on the side of cancer.
好了, Ted, 我给你
找到机会帮助别人
Okay,Ted,I found a way for you to help someone.
做点好事
To do some good.
这是Walter, Walter无家可归
This is Walter. Walter is homeless.
Walter想要一个大腿舞
And Walter would like a lap dance.
你在开玩笑吗?
Are you joking?
我从来不拿严肃的
I never joke about the
讥讽艺术开玩笑
sublime art of burlesque entertainment.
不, Barney, 这太不正常了
No,Barney,that's insane.
先生, 你希望我给你买
Sir,would you like me to buy you
自助餐的票吗?
a ticket to the buffet?
不, 我很饱了
No,I'm stuffed.
只要大腿舞就好了
Just a lap dance will be fine.
Ted, Walter已经去过
三所食物庇护所了
Ted,Walter's been to three shelter dinners.
你知道他哪里没去过吗?
You know where he hasn't been?
和Samantha去天堂
To heaven with Samantha.
听着, 这是今天唯一的机会
Look,it's the one chance you've
去帮助人了
had all day to help someone in need.
那么, 让这个人享受大腿舞吧
Now,buy this man a lap dance.
你说你想在别人
You said you wanted to see
眼中看到愉快
the look of joy in someone's eyes.
你知道, 我不觉得我会去看
You know,I don't think I'm going to watch.
去吧, Walter
Here you go,Walter.
感恩节快乐
Happy thanksgiving.
谢谢你
Thank you so much.
不, 真心的
No,really.
谢谢你
Thank you.
感恩节快乐, 伙计们
Happy thanksgiving,guys.
十一月的感恩节
Thanksgiving in November.
太怪了
Weird.
那就是2005年的感恩节
So,that was Thanksgiving 2005
说实话，过的并不开心
To be honest, it didn't go great,
生活中有很多开心的事情
But life has plenty of good parts
感恩身边一起生活的人
才是比较困难的部分
It's the rough parts that make you thankful you have people to share it with
--------------------------
******       ******
**********   **********
************* *************
*****************************
***************************
***********************
*******************
***************
***********
*******
***
*
--------------------------
-==cece&飞飞字幕组==-
LOVE
-==The Words of Love for My Dear Baby==-
how i met your mother
Season 1 Episode 9
嘿 我看见你为那个家伙做的了
Hey.I saw what you did for that guy.
那太不错了
It was really sweet.
噢... 想跳个舞吗?
Oh... do you want a dance?
呃, 不了, 谢了
Uh,no,thanks.
你想来点番薯吗?
Do you want some yams?
不了, 谢谢
No,thanks.
我是Amber
I'm Amber.
我是Ted
I'm Ted.
事实上... 我叫Tracy
Actually... I'm Tracy.
我还是Ted
Still Ted.
这个, 孩子们, 就是
And that,kids,is the
我遇见你们妈妈的故事
true story of how I met your mother.
什么?!
What?! What?!
我开个玩笑
I'm kidding.